# Djarwo Eko Prasojo

Tangerang, Banten, Indonesia



djarwoprasojo@gmail.com



081807877877



linkedin.com/in/djarwo-prasojo

# Summary

Software Engineer, I have 5 years experience in different IT field and 5 years as program engineer. I like new technologies and study them in depth everything about programming, so that my experience and knowledge is kept up to date.

I can also little speak english both oral and verbal. And now my last position is a Technical Lead Software Engginer. I have experience as a full stack developer (Mobile Developer, Front-End Developer, Back-End Developer & Devops).

### **Experience**



#### Lead Software Engineer

PT. Digerati Atomic Indonesia

Apr 2019 - Present (3 years 10 months)

Responsible for driving the development efforts to meet customer requirements and ensure that projects are completed on time and within budget. This article will provide a thorough outline of the job responsibilities, qualifications, and expectations associated with the lead developer position.

my responsibility include:

- Working closely with senior stakeholders to understand business requirements and help translate these into technical requirements for the development team.
- Planning and documenting technical specifications for features or system design.
- Designing, building, and configuring applications to meet business process and application requirements.
- Directing the development team in the design, development, coding, testing, and debugging of applications.
- Writing testable, scalable, and efficient code and leading code reviews.
- Mentoring junior team members and ensuring they adhere to determining software quality standards.

# **Software Engineer**

PT Dapur Rumah Sejahtera / Twiscode

Aug 2018 - Feb 2019 (7 months)

- 1. Build an app called Wahyoo
- 2. Build Wahyoo's Dashboard Admin
- 3. Wahyoo has 5 path of its part (Store, Sales, Courier, B2B and Customer parts). Ensure each part was build perfectly

#### Rackend Programmer

PT. Kuryotech Indonesia Jan 2018 - Aug 2018 (8 months) Create and Develop a Start Up or Company Profile application

www.beoku.com, Yii2 Based Framework with Postgres and Silverstripe databases.

Kuryotech in addition to being a start up company is also engaged in SoftwareHouse, so for orders and workmanship of the startup application, web profile.

#### Full Stack Developer

PT. KOKEK

Sep 2017 - Jan 2018 (5 months)

Creating a WEB-Based Internal Consultant Application

Using PHP CI Framework, With Tampot Bootstrap, Jquery, Ajax, Mysql, Handsontable, SavetToPdf, Export Import, and Serialize.

# IT Support Specialist

PT FTF Globalindo

May 2015 - Jun 2017 (2 years 2 months)

As IT support,

do the training program and implement it to the customer.

Discust with customers about custom programs.

Conducting Quality Control on custom programs and products.

Edit the report and module in the program.

Experienced Implementation outside of the special island in Eastern Indonesia, because almost all major cities in eastern Indonesia have been implemented for the program.

# Computer Technician

Gamma microtech computer

Jun 2012 - 2015 (3 years)

Work as Computer and Hardware Repair

- -Troubleshooting Computers and networks
- -Fix Printer
- -Setting LAN and WAN
- -In Computer Software Installation
- -Shoot Soft and Computer Harware

#### **Education**



#### Universitas 17 Agustus 1945 Surabaya

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2013 - 2017

#### Skills

Microsoft Power BI • Unit Testing • Linux • Red Hat Linux • Linux Kernel • Back-End Web Development • Front-End Development • Tailwind CSS • Microsoft SQL Server • MySQL